Guide to the H. Thomas Hickerson papers, 1974-2006.
Hickerson, H. Thomas papers,1972-2006.
- Series I: Subject Files and Correspondence
  - Subseries I: Department of Manuscripts and University Archives (M&A) / Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections (RMC)
    - NEH - Division of Pres. & Access (Box 19)
    - Network Costs (Box 19)
    - Networked Resources Redefinition Implementation (Box 19)
    - NHPRC / UNC Project (Box 19)
    - NEH - Division of Pres. & Access (Box 20)
    - Network Costs, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Networked Resources Redefinition Implementation, 2001 (Box 20)
    - NHPRC Electronic Records Project, 2000 (Box 20)
    - NHPRC / UNC Project, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Networks, Campus, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Nikolai, 1992 (Box 20)
    - National Sceince Digital Library (NSDL), 2004 (Box 20)
    - NSF International Digital Libraries Program, 2002 (Box 20)
    - NSF Project - Math Books, 1999 (Box 20)
    - NSF Proposal (unfunded), 2001 (Box 20)
    - Nuremberg Trial Transcripts, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Olin-Uris Redesign (Box 20)
    - OAIS: General Concepts (Box 20)
    - Open Access, Report of the Task Force, 2004 (Box 20)
    - Open Archives Initiative, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Open Knowledge Initiative, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Oxford University Library, 2002 (Box 20)
    - "Partners in Pedagogy", 2003 (Box 20)
    - Pelika, Michael - Review, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Pew Foundation Study: "The Internet Goes to College" (Box 20)
    - Pedagogy Online Discovery System (PODS), NSE / JISC (Joint Information Systems Committee) (Box 20)
    - Portal Implementation / K. Calhoun ARL Paper (Box 20)
    - Position Descriptions (Box 20)
    - President and Provost Office Documents Management, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Primary Source Media, 1998 (Box 20)
    - Priority Objectives, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
    - PROLA - Phys. Rev., 2005 (Box 20)
    - Public Affairs, 1997 (Box 20)
    - Public Ports (Computing), 2002 (Box 20)
    - Public / Staff Computing in the Library (Box 20)
    - Race & Religion Websites, 2003 (Box 20)
    - RBMS (Rare Books and Manuscripts) / ACRL (Associatino of College and Research Libraries), 2003 (Box 20)
    - RBMS - Montreal Pre-Conference (Box 20)
    - Research Libraries Group (RLG), 2000 (Box 20)
    - RLG Institutional Reposition Forum, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Reed, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Reidy, James, 2004 (Box 20)
    - Rhodes Hall Power Outage, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Rieger, Oya, 2002 (Box 20)
    - RLG, 2004 (Box 20)
    - RLG - CMI, 2001 (Box 20)
    - RMC - Capital Equipment Alliance (Box 20)
    - RMC - Public Service Head Candidate, 2000 (Box 20)
    - RMC - Reorganization Chart, 1998 (Box 20)
    - Rose Goldson Archive, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Rosenkrantz, Marcy, 2004 (Box 20)
    - SAA Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Safire Group, Endeavor, 2000 (Box 20)
    - SagaNet, 2001 (Box 20)
    - SagaNet, 2000-2001 (Box 20)
    - SagaNet / Mellon Usability Study, 2001 (Box 20)
    - SAA Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 20)
    - SAA Annual Meeting, 2002 (Box 20)
    - Safire / Endeavor, 1999 (Box 20)
    - SAA, 1999-2000 (Box 20)
    - SAA Fellows Group, 2000 (Box 20)
    - SAA, 1999 (Box 20)
    - SAA Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 20)
    - SAA Presidency, 1997 (Box 20)
    - SAA Presidential Address, 2001 (Box 20)
    - SAA - Hickerson, 2000 (Box 20)
    - Salaries, 1999-2001 (Box 20)
    - Sapphire Group Meeting, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Security, Computer (Box 20)
    - Scholarly Communications, 2003 (Box 20)
    - Scholarly Publishing in the Humanities, 2004 (Box 21)
    - Society of Southwest Archivists - Austin, Texas (Box 21)
    - Scholarly Publishing and Academic Resources Coalition (SPARC), 2002 (Box 21)
    - Special Collections Survey - ARL, 1998 (Box 21)
    - System for Tracking Administrative Records for Students (STARS), 2005 (Box 21)
    - Stockholm Presentation, 2001 (Box 21)
    - Strategic Decision Making - Johnson School Course, 2004 (Box 21)
    - Sun Grant, 2000 (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Patrick (Box 21)
    - St. Petersburg Trip Information, 2003 (Box 21)
    - Streaming Media Management (Box 21)
    - Sun Grant, 2000 (Box 21)
    - Sun Microsystems, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Sun Microsystems: Digital Media Universe, 2004 (Box 21)
    - Sun Ray Implementation, 2001 (Box 21)
    - Taiga, 2006 (Box 21)
    - Teaching and Learning with Technology, 2003-2004 (Box 21)
    - Technical Services Integration, 2003 (Box 21)
    - Technical Services Integration / RMC, 2005 (Box 21)
    - Tibbo, Helen (Box 21)
    - U.S. Congress Testimony (Box 21)
    - Voyager Implementation, 1999 (Box 21)
    - University Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 21)
    - uPortal, 2002 (Box 21)
    - Uris Library Renovation, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Vet / RMC Candidates, 2001 (Box 21)
    - Visual Image Collections, CU, 2005 (Box 21)
    - Warner, Simeon, 2001 (Box 21)
    - Wason Collection Digitizing, 2001 (Box 21)
    - Web Bridge Review, 2005 (Box 21)
    - Web Production Group, 2002 (Box 21)
    - Wireless, 2002 (Box 21)
    - Zwickler, Phil, 2004 (Box 21)
    - SAA - SagaNet Session, 1999 (Box 21)
    - RBMS, 1992 (Box 21)
    - RBMS, 1993 (Box 21)
    - RBMS - Executive Committee, 1993 (Box 21)
    - RBMS, 1992-1993 (Box 21)
    - RBMS Preconference, 1990 (Box 21)
    - RBMS Preconference, 1988 (Box 21)
    - RBMS Committee, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Human Sexuality Presentation, RBMS (Box 21)
    - RBMS Information Exchange, 1995 (Box 21)
    - RBMS Conference Development Committee, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Rare Book School, 1989 (Box 21)
    - Research Leave, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Rochester Presentation (Box 21)
    - Rockefeller Archives, 1982 (Box 21)
    - University of Virginia Consultancy, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Syracuse University, 1996 (Box 21)
    - SCRLC - Archival Automation Systems - Paper, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Southwest Archivists, Society of, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Penn, Arthur S. (Box 21)
    - Rawlings, Hunter R. III, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Rudin, Gail & Stephen, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Seattle Public Library, 1997 (Box 21)
    - Severinghaus, Leslie R., 1994 (Box 21)
    - Seznec, Alan, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Soules, Amy, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Springer, Verlag, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Stein Endowment - Wallach, 1997 (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Robert C. - Family Papers, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Tishman Proposal, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Witchcraft Digital Publications (Box 21)
    - Newman, F.R. Archival Fund (Box 21)
    - Library Budget, 1995-1996, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
    - Handel, Mark, 1994 (Box 21)
    - AMICO, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Columbia Meeting, 1997 (Box 21)
    - Corbis / Museum, 1997 (Box 21)
    - MDLC, 1997 (Box 21)
    - MESL, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Museum On-Line Project (Box 21)
    - Image/CU (Box 22)
    - Tishman Project, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Digital Access Coalition (Box 22)
    - Abbe, Elfriede, 1996 (Box 22)
    - American Antiquaries Society, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Biblioteca Virtual Miguel de Cervantes, 1999 (Box 22)
    - Brothers, Joyce, 1998 (Box 22)
    - CIDC, 1998-1999 (Box 22)
    - Colman, Gould Retirement, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Cornell University History, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Creation Station Project, 1999 (Box 22)
    - Digital Archiving Projects (Box 22)
    - Digital Library Federation, 1999 (Box 22)
    - D-LIT (Digital Library and Inforamtion Technologies) Management (Box 22)
    - Diners Club Card, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Distributed Access to Scholarly Material, 1996 (Box 22)
    - DRAMMA Project, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Euclid Project (Box 22)
    - Fabit, 1999-2000 (Box 22)
    - Ferreira, Joan, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Fine Arts Library Transfer, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Franklin, Carol Gittlin '61, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Full-Test Resource Assessment (Box 22)
    - Frick Project, 1999 (Box 22)
    - Getty Proposal, 1995 (Box 22)
    - GSRT, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Houghton Library, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Iceland / U.S. Millennium Events, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Icelandic Collection, 1995-96 (Box 22)
    - Icelandic Project, 1994-1995 (Box 22)
    - Icelandic Project, 1995-1998 (Box 22)
    - Icelandic Digital Library, 1998 (Box 22)
    - SagaNet Meeting, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Icelandic Project - Final Copy, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Interlibrary Library Loan of Archives and Special Collections, 1993 (Box 22)
    - IT - Tom, 1998 (Box 22)
    - IT - NDS, 1999 (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Herbert F. Art Museum, 1996 (Box 22)
    - LC-MOA (Library of Congress) Project (Box 22)
    - Librarian Search, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Library Budget, 1994-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 22)
    - Lindseth, Jon, 1998 (Box 22)
    - LMS Evaluation, 1998 (Box 22)
    - LMT, 1997-98 (Box 22)
    - LMT, 1998-1999 (Box 22)
    - Lowry, Judith, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Lynn, M. Stuart (Box 22)
    - MacConckle, Carol & Mac, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Making of America, 1997 (Box 22)
    - Making of America II, 1998 (Box 22)
    - Mandell, Judy & Jerry, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Mann, Tom and Diann, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Markle Foundation, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Mellon Foundation, 1996 (Box 22)
    - MESL (Museum Educational Site Licensing Project) / Cornell, 1996 (Box 22)
    - MESL Meeting, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Miller, Erica T. (Box 22)
    - Personnel Files (Box 23)
    - Personnel Files (Box 23)
    - Personnel Files (Box 23)
    - Personnel Files (Box 23)
    - Personnel Files (Box 23)
    - Various Correspondence, 1988-90 (Box 23)
    - Functional Requirements of the Manuscripts and Archives System - Yale University Library, 1981 (Box 23)
    - Japan Education and Research Conference, 2000 (Box 23)
    - Networked Access to Multimedia Collections: A Record of Achievement, 1994-1996 (Box 23)
    - National Information Systems Task Force (NITSF) Papers, 1981-84 (Box 23)
    - Kroch Security (Box 23)
    - Icelandic Curator Search, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Request for a Proposals for an Integrated Library System for CU Libraries, 1984 (Box 23)
    - A Proposed MARC Format for Archives and Manuscript Materials, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Interactive Multimedia Group / Cornell RMC Reports (Box 23)
    - Machine Readable Records, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Sun Microsystems Conference, 2005 (Box 23)
    - RMC Strategic Plan, 1994-97 (Box 23)
    - Cornell News Advisory, 1999 (Box 23)
    - Records Survey, Summer 1976 (Box 23)
    - Farewell to Tom Hickerson (DVD), 2006 (Box 23)
- Series II: Digital Access Coalition (DAC)
  - DAC Files: Museum Educational Site Licensing (MESL) Project (Box 7)
- Series III: Professional Organizations
  - Subseries 1: Society of American Archivists (SAA)
    - General Files (chronological), 1974-1980 (Box 8)
    - General Files (chronological), 1981-1988 (Box 9)
    - National Information Systems Task Force (NITSF) Files (Box 9)
    - SAA Council Files, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
    - SAA Council Files, 1994-1998 (Box 10)
  - Subseries 2: ALA/SAA Joint Committee
    - ALA/SAA Joint Committee files, 1988-1992 (Box 11)
  - Subseries 3: Research Libraries Group (RLG)
    - RLG Files, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
    - RLG Files, 1984-1986 (Box 12)